<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="help_contents">
        <item>Buttons and Icons</item>
        <item>Navigation</item>
        <item>Context menus</item>
        <item>Color controls</item>
        <item>Pick colors from an image</item>
        <item>Actions with a color</item>
        <item>Adjust font and background</item>
        <item>Favorites</item>
        <item>Full screen mode option</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="help_description">
        <item>_</item>
        <item>_</item>
        <item>
            Long press on the color to open context menu.
            Actions you can perform with the color are shown in the picture below.
        </item>

        <item>
            Moving handles set desired value of the parameter.
            Linear control: For finer tuning use buttons.
            Click on the button will change parameter by 1.
            Holding the button will move the handle smoothly.
            Round control: press the central button to set initial values of sat, val and opacity.
        </item>

        <item>
            To open any image from the device memory click on the \"Gallery\" icon (on top of the screen).\n
            Chosen picture you can expand or shrink (using two fingers),
            And move it across the screen holding with a finger.
            It allows to pick a color precisely.\n
            The click on the image will display a color from the point that been clicked,
            and the "aim" will jump to that point.
        </item>

        <item>
            Click icon \"i\" (1) to open color in the \"Fullscreen\" mode.
            Parameters of the color will be displayed
            (For returning just click any place). There is also possible to open "Full screen" mode
            if to "fling" color to the left / right.\n
            You have three options to save the color in the \"Favorites\" a) \"Draw\" V on the color (5)
            b) \"Double click\" on the color c) Via context menu (\"Long press\" on the color)\n
            If the color has been saved the tag with a little heart will appear on it (2).\n
            To send the color(s) parameters via email or messenger click the \"Send\" (3) icon.\n
            The click on the \"Blur\" icon (4) adds the opacity regulator to the linear control,
            and the click on the same (but \"crossed out\") icon will return the control
            to initial state (the color(s) will become opaque 100%).\n
            Any color you can set as a \"Wallpaper\" on your device.
            Just \"draw\" a \"heart\" (6) on the color or via context menu.
        </item>

        <item>
            Distinction in the \"Font and background\" mode:\n
            Clicks on the icon \"Flip to front\" (1)
            will connect the regulators or to the font or to the background.\n
            In the \"Adjustable font\" screen the slider (2) will change the font size,
            And clicks on the \"B\" or the \"I\" icons will change \"boldness\" or \"obliquely\"
            of the font accordingly.\n
        </item>

        <item>
            Click any color to open it in the \"Full Screen\"
            (then you can fling the screen to the left / right
            to get next or previous color accordingly).\n
            \"Long click\" on any color to select it for sending or deleting.
            Chosen colors will be marked by \"V\" sign (5).
            If at least one color is selected, simple click on the color will select (or deselect) it.\n
            You can choose all saved colors simultaneously by clicking on the \"Select all\" (1) icon.\n
            Also, if at least one color is selected, three new icons will appear on the action bar:\n
            (2) \"Undo\" - simultaneously deselects all marked colors;\n
            (3) \"Delete\" - pops up the dialog: \"All checked colors will be erased. Proceed?\";\n
            (4) \"Send\" - for sending parameters of colors that have been selected
            via email or Messenger.
        </item>

        <item>
            Click on the icon \"-\" (3) to hide parameters of the color, And click on the icon \"+\" (1) to open the parameters.\nIcon \"Send\" is for sending color parameters via email or Messenger.\nTo return to the previous screen just click any place.\nIf you came to the \"Full screen\" mode from the "Favorites", Flip the color to review saved colors.
        </item>

    </string-array>

    <array name="help_buttons">
        <item>Open navigation drawer and navigate through the app screens.</item>
        <item>Go to previously opened screen.</item>
        <item>Send color(s) parameters via email or messenger.</item>
        <item>Show the color\' opacity regulator.</item>
        <item>Hide the color\' opacity regulator.</item>
        <item>Click on this icon will open color(s) in the \"Fullscreen\" mode
            and provide color\' parameters.
        </item>
        <item>Pick a photograph taken by the device camera or an image from a gallery.</item>
        <item>Indicates that this color has been saved to favorites.
            Click on this icon to open the \"Favorites\" screen.
        </item>
        <item>Shows a point on the image that has been clicked. Color from this point is displayed.
            Clicking on other points will move the \"Aim\".
            It\'s also possible to move the image under the \"Aim\".
        </item>
        <item>Reset values of the color parameters (saturation, value and opacity) to 100%.
            (For the "round" color control only)
        </item>
        <item>Move the font to front for color adjusting.</item>
        <item>Move the background to front for color adjusting.</item>
        <item>Bold / Normal font selector.</item>
        <item>Roman / Italic font selector.</item>
        <item>In the \"Fullscreen\" mode reveals color(s) parameters info.</item>
        <item>In the \"Fullscreen\" mode hides color(s) parameters info.</item>
        <item>In the \"Favorites\" mode deletes \"checked\" colors.</item>
        <item>In the \"Favorites\" mode shows that color is \"checked\" for sending or deleting.
        </item>
        <item>In the \"Favorites\" mode is used for selecting all colors.</item>
        <item>In the \"Favorites\" mode is used for deselecting all selected colors.</item>
    </array>

    <array name="help_navigation">
        <item>Open \"Two colors\" screen</item>
        <item>Open \"Linear control\" screen</item>
        <item>Open \"Round control\" screen</item>
        <item>Open \"Color from an image\" screen</item>
        <item>Open \"Adjustable font\" screen</item>
        <item>Open \"Regular font\" screen</item>
        <item>Open \"Settings\" screen</item>
        <item>Open \"Favorite colors\" screen</item>
        <item>Open \"Help\" screen</item>
    </array>

</resources>